

Kimberly Swaby

Business, Sales & Marketing Officer

876 861 6117 · kimberlyvb1@yahoo.com

HobbiesRunning, aerobics, and reading.

Profile

I am an energetic and goal oriented Business Development Officer, and have almost twenty years experience in the financial services industry. The role encompasses sales, customer relations and account management. The BDO is responsible for informing potential and existing customers of company promotions, products and services as well as to continually identify new sales opportunities.

The necessary skills are:

Strong analytical and problem solving skills.

Strong communication skills

Strong human relation skills.

Strong sales and marketing skills

Excellent customer service skills

Excellent Time Management skills

Good organizational skills

Ability to work under pressure and handle multiple tasks

My previous roles within the company were: Receptionist, Teller, Memebr Services Officer, M.I.S. (Projects) and Marketing Exposition Officer.

Employment History

Business Development Officer, COK Sodality Co-Operative Credit Union, Kingston

January 2003 — Present

The role of the Business Development Officer (BDO) is to generate new business for the company. Additionally, the BDO is a point of contact for existing clients, and offers financial advise and general account management.

Receptionist, City Eyewear (England), Bradford

January 1999 — February 2002

The receptionists task was to answer customers queries , meet and greet customers and file documents.

Cashier, Welcome Supermarket, Kingston

April 2002 - July 2002

The cashier's duty was to accept payment for goods purchased, answer customer's queries and assist with the training of new cashiers.

Promoter, Amalgamated Distributors Ltd, Kingston

July 2002 — December 2002

The promoter's role was to drive sales at venues and answer customer's queries.

Education

Guidance & Counselling, International University of the Caribbean (IUC), Kingston

October 2021

The Guidance & Counselling Bsc. was a 3 year programme that had both theoretical and practical elements that dealt with the pschology of human behaviour and how to bring about change in people's circumstances when they are under duress.

Business Studies, Bradford College, Bradford

January 1999 - August 2001

The certificate in Business Studies introduced concepts in the management of business and office procedures.

Additional modules within the course was:

I.T.

Mathematics

Spoken English

Word Processing

References

Nicholas Clarke from COK Sodality 876 445 9452 · nclarke@cokcu.com

Dagmar Berry from Q&S Enterprise (Jamaica) Ltd 876 881 5459 · <u>qandsenterprise@gmail.com</u>

Courses

Professional Selling Skills, HRM Options Group International Ltd

Online Securities Course, The Jamaica Stock Exchange

Anti-Money Laundering/Counter Financing of Terrorism, COK Sodality Credit Union Ltd